oh I saw that steaming I thought
something was on fire
pandas was on fire two people no chats
oh wait someone subscribe like pay me
money I love when people do that yeah
and that's no one even talked no could
you guys talk to make sure chats working
Oh someone talked wait I don't know
where everybody yes maybe I didn't act
maybe it didn't actually send the
notification or something maybe those
are just the people refreshing my twitch
stream oh did we mess up and not send a
notification oh yeah buddy we got people
buddy the twitch servers slow today are
you a subscriber do you pay money a
tier-one oh I love when people subscribe
to my stream I get money they get well
and that's Twitter's problem right yeah
Noel bars now we're being watched
take a look take a look have you watched
no no just show them the watching yeah
yeah no I was distracted I was using my
phone don't worry we say if I had Alex
watch the road and it was yelling at me
that's because they're good driver
monitoring's wait is it prime exclusive
good eye wait but not many people are
talking oh yeah yeah go to settings do I
actually have maybe it's still armed
from last time oh you have to be a
subscriber to talk sometime we do that
sometimes but maybe you can turn that
off in settings this is terrible you
know what it's subscriber only today
everybody better subscribe and I'm
really sorry about this but I really
don't know this is paola chat will ask
will answer any of your deeply personal
questions right now right here on
exclusive chat guys honestly if we knew
how to turn exclusive shut off we would
but I think all you can do now is
subscribe if you want to chat welcome
welcome to the talking party oh no don't
worry my mods will show off and they'll
be banned to typos but subscribers are
good people and they don't deserve
answer times
wow that's that's I love when you guys
subscribe to my channel you could show
me open pilot show me
I see open pilot yeah oh yeah we gotta
get some of that microfiber cloth oh I
have a cold so I can barely hear out of
my left ear my right ear but we got to
heal up guess we got a lot of great
things planned for CES we're on our way
to Vegas right now we set a course in
the open pilot we just typed in Las
Vegas because we have the secret good
version of open pilot and it's gonna
drive side to what's happening at CES
well with us or with everybody
I went I've been to CES twice before the
first year the big thing they were
advertising is yeah go yellow pixels on
TVs like like like I think it was like
sharp they spent that was the big ad
campaign around everywhere yellow now of
course you know this makes no sense
all right like red green and blue can
capture you only have three cones in
your eye always for women the yellow
we're have four well they should buy
yellow TV and they just have like yellow
pictures and it was so stupid so that's
what happened to see yes that year and
also my buddy lost eight thousand
dollars playing casino war that happened
oh come on broski get in your lane he
was not his thing he was over-the-line
and then the next year I went he lost
way more and now we're not gonna go
there but but you know bros casino Wars
a great game and Tom tell that story
moving the time we played like those
people playing war and they were all
betting like ten dollars and I just
showed up put on dollars down and played
one game of war gotta ace and then live
in my line is that good oh yeah I
crushed it I crushed it
what do you mean no okay so where I
don't like hype is like in the medical
field right like like like pipe in the
medical field is disgusting
the theranos um but consumer electronics
is hype like it's honest you know what
you know you guys know what I really
don't like is dishonesty the people who
are hypocrites but like people are
supposed to get hyped about ok the
yellow TVs were kind of but
like some consumer electronics are
really cool you should get hyped about
subscriber only chat is really getting
us so many so many subs today people
want to talk and then the next year I
went to CES no I'm the president pros
but like I say I'm not like the
president of like a first world modern
democracy I'm like the president of like
the Democratic People's Republic of
Congo and you know the more they put
Democratic and people's in the title the
last legitimate the country is it's true
People's Republic of China versus
Republic of China Democratic People's
Republic of Korea versus Republic of
Korea but so yeah I'm one of those like
third-world
presidents who rules with an iron fist
and doesn't feel like he serves the
population we have a booth they know we
have a booth right what's 25 20 but
we're in the smart cities section
because we didn't yeah yeah so you know
man
hi Breathitt Sucker Free get hyped
yo Pat stay look him up you don't know
Pat today is this is a pat stay over the
break Sucker Free get height you know
what rhymes with Sucker Free talkin me
yeah we all a change bros come to 0-7
one is that guys subscribers asking oh
that's right everyone subscribers
talking so I'm gonna honestly answer all
your questions probably around xx look a
little before that see like like this
guy's driving slow so we're just kind of
passing see I just put the blinker on I
touched the wheel I'm making a lane
change
oh yeah changing lanes monitor other
vehicles it doesn't watch the vehicles
for you yeah ever you don't need that
that's what you have eyes for we
outsource to the human you see in the
future humans will work for robots you
know and they get you in by like and
this is like what it's like to have a
company right like you think your
employees work for you but the truth is
you work for them it's like the same way
with this right like you think that the
computers work for you but soon you're
gonna you working for them yeah buddy
what do you want to shout at the screen
okay we'll get we'll get pulled over for
too many lane changes
don't think they'll think we've been
smoking back Oh
what are these what's pedestrian
heatsink this is someone who's talking
about wanting an IR camera on discord
last night do you have a IR camera no
can you drive car yes don't need will be
mine the same buddy now I really
snapping I'm religious I just don't like
atheists you know nah a theists are all
like all non-religious I'm not religious
but then they're just a theists and
that's like a religion I think we should
just tag all the deer and then you can
subscribe to deer net and it'll tell you
where the deer are deer become on the
IOT that's if you click somebody watch
survivalist I do anything special on I
fell asleep before we really got to
whether the Sasquatch is real or not but
I would say that
Sasquatch being real is more real than
honey healing burns and more real than
than fluids treating illnesses that's
how real I say sasquatches but I'd say
it's less real than an increase in
carbon dioxide it's probably about as
real I'd say I'd say yeah yeah it's
medium real Tuesday is the first act no
we're doing we're doing a big live
stream on Tuesday guys so make sure make
sure to turn in tuned into the common AI
YouTube if you don't subscribe over
there go now come an archive go to the
official comment a I YouTube make sure
to subscribe you know what I was just
stressing out like before when I thought
it was driving badly it's just cuz
that's all I was paying attention to oh
my god don't change lanes I was driving
beautifully I haven't even thought about
the driving for a long time no no I
don't have Disney Plus yeah I have Nick
heads yeah yeah let's rewatch half a
Twitter last airbender yeah if you get
into a crash because you are watching a
video instead of the road
what video and you haven't been the uber
driver killed somebody while watching
The Voice to test the guy hit a truck
while watching Harry Potter oh yeah yeah
Harry Potter was discovered at the scene
of the crash still playing on the
portable DVD player I laughed because
it's sad
we didn't see it good that's a job for
the cars no it's like doing talking oh
it's just twitch and carplay doesn't
work well so we can't actually see our
mouths per gallon but I think this car
gets like 40 on the highway yeah it's
pretty good now we're gonna have to stop
for dance at some point guys like okay
so I branded it in 2019 I called
insanity 2019 Saturday 2019 you notice
how all like the like sjws just died in
2019 like it was just over like sanity's
back right and no it's just like like
everybody just came to a nice middle
ground 2020 I really think is gonna be
the year of the death of hype like I
used to talk about height because hype
was a threat I don't think hypes a
threat anymore
I think a lot of hype died last year to
the new things are excited to get hyped
about you go through the hype cycle
alright the beginning of the hype cycle
is exciting we love to get hyped about
new exciting things that sounds about
right
um nah but in like 2020 like zukes is
going out of business this year
vishal prediction zooks goes that well
no Suk's gets aqua hired I think so yeah
some car company maybe even by way mo or
cruise now cruise cruise is sad I was
like like people have read people and
read a self-driving cars or see again
people are self-driving cars are seeing
it now like oh yeah they've become much
more reasonable they were unreasonable
to be kidding oh they were Tesla haters
I mean no you still the occasional Tesla
hater Weibo has actually made some
progress what his crew showed in the
last year's should do a review reviews
yo we're here for that we're here from
the George Hotz twitch channel to review
mobile I can you let us up to this booth
no no mobile I last you had like a
little castle the last time I was there
I did let me end yeah all right astray
how pleasant to subscriber only chat I
think this should always be a thing I
just I feel like we're just chilling
with cool people cuz their subscribers
house way Mo's progress oh you guys want
to hear something terrible
[Laughter]
how's way most progress put it this way
if whammo had spent fifty million
dollars to get to where they are right
now
way more be a good company if Wayne
would raised fifty billion a 50 million
50 million but no instead I've spent
like ten billion so yeah they're off by
like you know fact there are twenty
twenty twenty let's play more than
twenty it's two hundred it's a really
big factor all right find a hundred
billion for fine wait so watch carefully
still have to start lane change
whoa I don't know it went back it got
freaked out and undid the lane change it
was kind of a normal human renew ver
something freaked it out we need
diversity is very important number
progressive
yo but as long as there's no glass
ceilings as long as they're not made out
of glass
so what that means what the lane change
I don't know I just freaked out a little
bit that was like a normal human thing
spindrift man look at the look for their
product placement in the new Veronica
Mars season they place things like spin
drift and then you wonder like we're
gonna really change ID for this truck
ready all right steer right to start
laying change let's go Oh point eight
figured it all out yet I have a few
things that I want one of the things
that bothers me is it's slowing down
four turns it needs to learn how to slow
down four turns better
yeah a lot of bugs a lot of little bugs
just need fixing I'm gonna start really
taking advantage of the fact that we're
getting all this data back from all the
people so it was the battle just a
competitor to Newton Mass Wow a battle
of water
oh you mean oh that disgusting one with
the ugly font wow that's crazy sounds
like going like crazy ever since that
note 7 blew up you know they've been
everywhere oh I did some refactoring oh
it did that not ship
I did some your wiry factors oh I guess
yes on zero 7 this is it's in the
eternal republic yeah serious curves
that's what you get when you have a
torque modded Civic Oh someone's gonna
break the glass floor though and that's
like you know you break the glass
ceiling that's bad if you break the
glass or a floor because there's nowhere
to go but down who broke the glass floor
[Music]
if only if only I decided to do things
whereas in commerce or publishing
because what do I get when we publish
it takes time and we don't get anything
it's not that I'm like we got to be
secretive about it but I'm like you know
we published some great stuff we publish
incredible stuff like when we when we do
that ie B analysis you know that took us
a lot of time as a company we were
really excited about it we put a medium
posting it's like a hundred collapse and
then I write up some trash just
insulting other self-driving car
companies 2400 collapse that's 24x more
collapse so the reason we don't publish
is because that's not what the people
appreciate know really like it's just
nothing useful research actually we do
publish we publish a new model almost
every release we don't really get those
engagements anymore yeah yeah no other
roads you definitely get them but on the
highway subscriber people get a lot of
slack because their subscribers but all
say is you know you gotta figure that
out yourself yeah exactly figure it out
yourself
yeah yeah if you're following someone's
guide how not to be a noob though you
know I do always recommend heavy how to
not fail at life quit bitching about the
bitches edition I do always I do always
recommend that that taught me a lot
about life guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh well it depends how many shares we
have no what's all right well well no no
no hang a negative so I can do this we
have six million outstanding shares if
we were to raise money now would
probably be it like let's say 300
million dollar valuation just because I
can do that math easier so six million
was 300 divided by six 50 so it's $50 a
share so yeah we're ways to go before
420 see we'd have to like we'd have to
like 10x our share price so oh yeah what
comes with a couple billion we thought
we'd have a wait there's some big exits
here I also have a coffee maker well we
don't we don't tell the twitch is about
my you know thing but we're not telling
them just because I was disengaging
while steering obviously that was a
disengagement that exit ramp is a
disengagement for drug trafficking he
moved he moved on to his next thing
[Laughter]
whatever he's into now
so yeah okay we had a disengagement for
an exit ramp yeah kind of well some of
us a breakfast I offered you breakfast
you're like no no it's not time for food
yet no I threw them out but you did yeah
in the car they're not right there's a
vault yo I test drove one of those ones
it's $40,000 and it has seats that you
have to do manually what vault no their
vaults with a fee I know they sound very
similar there's how many sad note
reviewers because everyone just wants to
talk no I don't you see you know what
they say about dreams if you fall
we have 309 viewers this is insane and
reviewers yo if you guys aren't
following me on instagram instagram
complex george hotz
mark zuckerberg told me that if i get
30,000 followers he'd give me a blue
checkmark and I'm not like eighteen
point four thousand snaps so I always
say thirty I wrote it on my LinkedIn
this proof
I round it up what can I say
catch me outside how about that lotions
and lace more affordable than divorce
while ya get a histogram get the
histogram out everywhere the lanes are
tiny I'm not posting more content
Alex this is like if I can't do it on my
terms I don't want to do it at all
because when she what no one's just hurt
no I don't even know Mattox I saw you
bypassing your screen time restriction
on Instagram this morning oh that guy
who oh should we start on the Navy oh
don't get me started on the Nate young
guys when do you think the last time the
Navy did anything was like like shot at
anything or like did anything we looked
it up 1988 man I don't even think return
to the Jedi came out yet
yo that was before the Berlin Wall fell
we could definitely say that yeah oh
yeah but then you know you could read
you know the Navy the Navy the Navy
crashed two boats like two years ago
like when's the last time there's been a
Navy battle all right but now we can't
rehash the Navy conversation the Navy
conversation only happened once
it's too hot all right all right yeah
hold guys does that count the secrets uh
bad tax have we done secret Sabha tax
wait just a spin draft now it's banana
as well yo you know what's crazy if I
was sleeping in the backseat
except for that exit we'd still be alive
right now don't do it I mean if your
chances of dying or high you shouldn't
do something current constantly all the
aircraft carriers are deployed how much
money is that costing me and what are we
blowing up with aircraft you guys know
the Air Force doesn't even do the drones
us the army was the Navy always joke was
the Navy always a joke someone like like
like back in the day and they wore those
uniforms the Navy used to be like a
serious I think the Navy went down with
the British Empire
that's totally a compliment and we like
to be chill and relaxed on this channel
that car got a little close to me so
that was a disengagement we trying to
kick the Russians off the internet wait
really
you mean the guys like sitting in like a
warehouse in New Mexico well Colorado
New Mexico deployed yeah they run
Windows XP welcome welcome to the
conversation yo if we just say
inflammatory stop people subscribe so
they can counter the inflammatory stuff
no no no Tory stop on the tour channel
wow I can't believe anyone like us watch
this more than when I'm on the computer
not even doing anything I'm literally
watching a car drive and complaining
about the Navy do you want you want to
just go to that convention center and
say were there yeah I know you want to
stop cuz you know unity breakfast I
offered you breakfast I made nice
guacamole this morning I had to use the
avocados so remember that's having
winter Burger King on periscope no no no
we went to Burger King on periscope once
way back in the day we went to a
McDonald's at a periscope together
wait why do you mean the time we went to
Denny's we periscoped in the Volvo
periscope was still a thing oh yeah I
was trying to sell the Volvo well look
how the lane disappeared it just it just
hangs on perfectly man this thing's good
technique here for the crash yo if
there's gonna be a crash I'm happy to do
in a live stream oh I've stream I wasn't
on the way to Vegas that was just that
night we went to McDonald's yeah my
mother watched that live ship it said
who's Alex she's be upset just like you
know my uncle was in the Navy or
something I don't know I don't know I
don't know anyone even me
well that uncle's an architect a he's
cool it's been driving itself forever we
don't even talk about it you know cuz if
you have a good self-driving car you
don't even talk about it you can have
this yourself if you just go on our
website and buy a yacht yeah you're
gonna need a compatible car but don't
worry there's like 65 book now so you
have a lot of choices
go to Barstow uh no tech lead okay I
thought it was like what you call like
yeah we know what tech lead is ya know
climate change is family weddings all
right
climate climate change is real but that
doesn't mean we have to do anything
about it that's that's a good meme I
think right I always want to piss off
you know like Republicans and Democrats
have ever told you about like my dream
of marrying a corporation is the
Democrats say marriage is for everyone
and the Republicans say corporations are
people right global warming is real but
we're not gonna do anything about it
boom lovin corporations like be like a
boring legal battle and like my marriage
my marriage would only be recognized in
like four states and Rhode Island they
recognize it but only if it's a civil
union
this seems like too much effort yeah but
what panic the disco was good
they were now he sucks it does collapse
with Taylor Swift no there ain't no I me
yes I know I T yes I know there is a but
there is of me yeah terrible
Oh yo that's a little that's you can't
marry your own corporate that's I don't
think that's okay
I wish you would all have automatically
changed lanes there to avoid this truck
that would have been really Pleasant I
[Applause]
don't think I can marry Tesla Tesla is a
bit you know out of my league you guys
you just missed two excellent lane
changes all the lane change features so
good it's what used to be disengagement
is now just not disengagement at some
point the future I have to pee and then
we can stop maybe they lost the service
how about we got a comment
you can't incorporate your spouse stuff
this big of established corporation
that's right it's kind of like if you
marry a corporation you like merge your
powers lightly you know marrying your
daughter off to the Prince of Denmark or
something no there's no princess anymore
who's making George mad what are they
saying
Wow
Walt that we have service man it's cuz I
have an iPhone 11 Pro
what are this comments oh no but no but
remember not all of them are subscribers
some of them can't talk because we don't
know how to turn that off well that's
not what we call it just sleeping with
other people
ethically and being chill about it is
not polyandry polyamory the whole thing
will get me started on polyamory it's
worse than the Navy no but what foods
you are what do you want you want subway
you want that terrible-smelling spread
pick where we're eating good poi twitch
twitch yeah
twitch plays eating which plays lunch
we're at that we're by a speed limit 70
signs now you can google we're at CA
trops
oh wait no here's a road show them the
side road yeah who are 215 that's true I
don't even remember where we are because
I haven't driven the car for like hours
yo possib I know I see his Mountain ears
are messed up because I have a cold I'll
take that guys I do way less drugs
and you all think
oh the new MacBooks display no no no the
new display and the new the cheese
grater well we have a trash can we got a
complete the Apple home where / now
because the drop is better than me
gusting OH
that's right that's right yeah
oh we gotta take that one what's the
time flies when you're streaming and
having fun with good people with stars
Nexen a Taco Bell franchise or corporate
arena then all Taco Bell's at the same
Wow we didn't go to San Diego San Diego
we're just in the right light I keep
thinking of that song Barlow girls the
best night is a terrible song it's not
pronounced Mimi it's pronounced me
[Laughter]
who set up who said I'm a tech people
wait go on about changes to the system
yeah we're gonna change the system one
point out we're at 0.7 now what's the
next big thing well it's not the Navy
I'll tell you that
[Laughter]
oh man it's really bad you know if you
know what it is we're going up Alex
you're always cold
you can unsink them and you can make
yours ha pasa bro oh wow so but really
we're going up and it's really bothering
my ears this is in Belgium I do not like
the impossible burgers and I'm not a
tech people so stop with that just
I have a complex nuanced identity
outside of tech No
yes everyone needs to be able to do that
programming challenge we don't like hire
any those people the only people who are
really hiring four people are gonna do a
bell because the futures ml no we would
also hire people
we'd also hire like oh my god oh no no
Matt you're just popped oh my you're
just popped ah ah that was pleasant wait
use your ear popped yes wait why don't
you just pop the same time we're so in
sync
it's like recycle together now what was
oh no no why are someone who's very good
with like SystemC stuff - there is
another way to get hired a comma as well
that we don't really talk about and
that's the mini pro request to open
pilot so like yeah like people who do
pull requests people have done car ports
we've discussed a hiring map yeah we
should put on the jobs page like it's
not just the programming challenge like
if you have a history of doing pull
request to open pilot where you want to
hire you the stream is alive and now
we're back thing good thing open pilot
doesn't require our constant internet
connection yeah yeah that's just a
people thing you don't got to put tack
before that
[Music]
we're full on the hardware team oh yeah
no okay so the programming challenge is
how you get hired for the research team
if you want to get hired for the open
pilot team submit pull requests to open
pilot don't get us started on settings
where a set settings we're coming out of
the hills complain we know people the
doubler well I know that bar yeah yeah
is he cool down the bar only in San
Francisco drinking is alive and well in
San Diego San Francisco's over man Oh
will open pilot stop for this bag Trash
Pack will open pilots slam on the brakes
for this trash bag
you know what would slam on the brakes
for trash bag lidar
yeah cuz its export control technology
know why DARS great we're stuck with
Lyde ours yeah okay our choices are
McDonald's or subway or neither they
keep going that's right that's the right
choice because it's the only one I would
have accepted I mean I might have
considered if you said McDonald's if you
would have said subway I just would have
made a face it's always disgusting
okay we have 11 viewers and I'm gonna
see if I can turn off there has to be a
way to turn off that moderator only
chest
no I don't even understand I'm not sure
ten on the web